(Amy:)I must say, Penny,
this is great fun.
(Penny:)Glad you're
enjoying yourself.
(Amy:)Until I met you and Bernadette,
my trips to the bathroom
(Amy:)had been entirely focused
on elimination.
(Amy:)Now they have a delightful
social aspect.
(Bernadette:)Amy, you must've been
in the bathroom
(Bernadette:)with other women before.
(Amy:)Of course I have.
(Amy:)But they were strangers
and seemed off-put
(Amy:)when I engaged in friendly
stall-to-stall chit-chat.
(Bernadette:)Some women don't
like to get chummy
(Bernadette:)when their panties are down.
(Amy:)You okay in there, bestie?
(Penny:)I'm fine...
(Amy:)The reason I ask is
that many people
experience bladder shyness;
(Amy:)the inability to pass uri...
(Penny:)Yeah, I said I'm fine.
Stop talking to me.
(Amy:)She always this crabby
when she urinates?
(Bernadette:)We're really not that close.
(Penny:)Screw it.
I'll go later.
(Amy:)And I'll be right
by your side.
(Bernadette:)Did I tell you
Priya invited